mp3lyrics.org 2009-02-21

# Mp3 Lyrics Organized : Privacy Policy

Mp3lyrics.org takes your privacy seriously. This policy covers how Mp3lyrics.org treats personal information that is collected and received. Please read the following to learn more about this privacy policy. 

### Personally identifying information

"Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address. You are never required to submit any such information. _You may choose_ to supply your email address when submitting or correcting lyrics, or when you want to contact mp3lyrics.org. However, this information is only stored for the sole purpose of enabling us to reply your requests. 

### Data collection

Mp3lyrics.org collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Mp3Lyrics.org _may_ use this information to operate, develop and improve its searching services. Such information is mainly used in aggregated form. An example of this is the number of users who searched for a specific term, to record what artists or songs that are popular. 

In addition to your browser information, mp3lyrics.org log your IP address or host name. Such information is used principally to track your location in the effort of displaying relevant advertisement, and in the effort of figuring out what crawlers are visiting this site. Your IP address or host name is only stored for a limited time, depending on your [HTTP](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP) / [IP](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_Protocol) behaviour, before it is deleted. 

### Cookies

During your visit to Mp3lyrics.org a cookie may be sent to your browser that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a completely harmless, small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your browser when you visit a website. Mp3Lyrics.org use cookies to improve the quality of this service and to better understand how people interact with this web site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you configure your browser to refuse cookies, some features at Mp3lyrics.org will not be working for you. However you will still be able to search for lyrics. You may read more about what cookies are and how they work at [Wikipedia's page on HTTP Cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie). To submit new lyrics, make contact or use our [song editing service](http://edit.mp3lyrics.org/) your browser has to support the use of cookies, and have this feature enabled! 

### JavaScript

This site uses JavaScript to, among other things, chiefly display good looking pages, track visitor information and behaviour, set cookies on your browser and display advertisement. To learn what JavaScript is visit [Mozilla's](http://developer.mozilla.org/en/About_JavaScript) or [Wikipedia's](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Javascript) explanations on JavaScript. 

### Caching

Mp3Lyrics.org use server caching to ease the load on the web server. Because of this some site updates may not be visible before a page expires or is removed from the server cache. In addition to server caching mp3lyrics.org tell your browser to use local caching. That is we send header (invisible) instructions to your browser telling it to cache each page (and other data) locally on your computer. This is to make subsequent page requests faster for you and to additionally ease the load on the server. Therefore you should **remember to always force reload pages on mp3lyrics.org if you want to see changes/page updates**. This is to prevent your browser from displaying the local cached page data. To _force reload (re-fresh)_ a page in your browser press and simultanously hold down the keys _ctrl + F5_ when you are looking at the page you want to force reload. Different [web browsers](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_Browser) tend to require different procedures for force reloading. But the above procedure usually works on most newest version browsers. You can read more about force reloading [here](http://support.wordpress.com/browser-issues/). 

### Information Sharing

Mp3Lyrics.org does not rent or sell any information that is collected of the surfers visiting this web site. 

### Information Security

Mp3Lyrics.org take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration of data. 

### Third Party Advertising

Mp3Lyrics.org use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements at mp3lyrics.org, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

Some quick notes about how our advertisers are using cookies: When you are first served an ad by mp3lyrics.org, the advertiser assigns you a unique number and records that number in the cookie file of your computer. Then, when you visit mp3lyrics.org, the advertiser reads this number to help target ads to you. The cookie can help ensure that you do not see the same ad over and over again. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site. This information helps our advertisers cater their ads to your needs.
